<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>KCSG Unbound - Extended Def Limit</name>
  <author>TeH_Dav</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>user.kcsg.unbound</packageId>
  <description>KCSG Unbound removes the 65,535 definition limitation in RimWorld, specifically targeting SymbolDefs used in procedural structure generation.

This mod allows you to use an unlimited number of structure generation symbols, solving a common problem in heavily modded games where structure generation stops working properly due to hitting the hard-coded limit.

Features:
- Bypasses the 65,535 def limit for SymbolDefs through custom registries
- Uses early Harmony patching to intercept def registration
- Includes a debug monitor to track the number of registered symbols
- Compatible with existing KCSG mods like Vanilla Expanded Framework

Technical details:
This mod targets the limitation caused by RimWorld's use of unsigned short (ushort) indices for definitions, which restricts the total to 65,535 entries (2^16-1). By providing an alternative registration system for SymbolDefs, the mod allows you to use any number of structure generation definitions without causing errors or corruption.

Recommended for players using many mods that add new settlement and structure generation content.

This mod was created with AI assistance using Claude 3.7 Sonnet. If you have issue with that, don't use this mod.</description>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <loadBefore>
	<li>bs.fishery</li>
	<li>oskarpotocki.vanillafactionsexpanded.core</li>
  </loadBefore>
</ModMetaData> 
